Guide to the Cornell University Library Academic Assembly records, 1969-2002.
Cornell University Library Academic Assembly records, 1969-2002
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Library Academic Assembly records, 1969-2002.
13-11-2508
Cornell University Library Academic Assembly
4 cubic ft.
Minutes, correspondence, audiocassettes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes, correspondence and resolutions of the Academic Assembly, 1969-1978; minutes of the Steering Committee, 1974-1979; and minutes of joint meetings of the Steering Committee and standing committees, 1977-1981; Economic Status Committee correspondence and reports 1973-93; Academic Orientation Committee records; Academic Personnel Policy Committee records 1975-90. Also, handouts from the Academic Assembly meeting, Feb. 13, 1990, presentation by the Support Staff Development Committee. Includes a chronology of the governance of the Cornell University Library; also, four audiocassettes of Academic Assembly programs, and the Compass logbook.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes, correspondence and resolutions of the Academic Assembly, 1969-1978; minutes of the Steering Committee, 1974-1979; and minutes of joint meetings of the Steering Committee and standing committees, 1977-1981; Economic Status Committee correspondence and reports 1973-93; Academic Orientation Committee records; Academic Personnel Policy Committee records 1975-90. Also, handouts from the Academic Assembly meeting, Feb. 13, 1990, presentation by the Support Staff Development Committee. Includes a chronology of the governance of the Cornell University Library; also, four audiocassettes of Academic Assembly programs, and the Compass logbook.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Libraries.; Cornell UniversityLibrary. Support Staff Development Committee.; Cornell UniversityLibrary. Committee on the Economic Status of Librarians.; Cornell UniversityLibrary. Academic Personnel Policy Committee.; Cornell UniversityLibrary. Academic Orientation Committee.
Subjects:
Academic Libraries--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Librarians--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Places:
Academic Libraries--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Academic Assembly: minutes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reports -- Continuing Education & Professional Growth, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Academic Work Week, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- History, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Steering Committee correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Reports -- Planning Council, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- procedure 13, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Committee on Composition of the Librarians Assembly, [1970] (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Faculty Status, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Ombudsman, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Academic Assembly -- Bylaws, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Report -- Continuing Education & Professional Growth, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Reports -- Library Study (Mineka Report), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Reports -- Organizational Behavior Research (Herker Report), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Faculty Membership, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Academic Staff, correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Biographical Directories, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Standing Committee on the Economic Status of Librarians, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ad Hoc Committee - Faculty Status, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- History, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Committee on Personal Leave, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Student-Library Staff Discussions, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Minutes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Academic Assembly -- Bylaws, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Reports -- Planning Council, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Academic Assembly -- resolutions, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Academic Assembly -- correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Academic Staff -- correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Academic Work Week, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Biographical Directory, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Economic Status of Librarians, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- History, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Library Trainees, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Orientation Program, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Professional Literature, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Standing Committee Duties, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Academic Assembly -- Steering Committee Election, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Steering Committee -- miscellany, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Minutes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Academic Assembly -- Bylaws, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Resolutions, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Reports -- Long Range Financial Planning (Cranch Report), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Reports -- Vincent Attitudinal Survey, 1973 (Box 1)
- Economic Status Committee -- correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Evaluation Procedures, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Instructing Library Users, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Professional Literature, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Research Leaves, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Standing Committee-- Duties, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Miscellaneous committees, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Proposed Trustee By-Law, committee reports, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Reports: Continuing Education & Professional Growth, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Resolutions, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee - Procedure 31 (Grievance Procedure), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Audio Visual Materials, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Economic Status Committee -- TIAA-CREF, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Evaluation Procedures, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 61-62)
- Evaluation Procedures for Academic Staff, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Orientation Program, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Research Leaves, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Standing Committee Nominations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Steering Committee -- correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Steering Committee -- election, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Steering Committee -- minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Miscellaneous Committees, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- ByLaws, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Proposed ByLaw, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Resolutions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 28 (Evaluation Procedures for Academic Staff), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 31 (Grievance procedure), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Committee on Economic Status of Librarians, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Evaluation Procedures, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Evaluation Procedures for Academic Staff, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Organizations and Procedures of the University Faculty, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Ad Hoc Committee - Professional Literature, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Standing Committee duties, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Current, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Miscellaneous Committees, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Cornell University --ByLaws (as amended through 10/8/1977), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Academic Assembly -- Resolutions, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 18 (Library Personnel Office Files, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 31 (Grievance Procedure), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Academic Assembly -- History, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Organization & Procedures of the University Faculty, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Standing Committee -- Duties, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Academic Assembly -- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Steering Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Steering Committee -- Nominations, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- "Current" (miscellany), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Miscellaneous Committees, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- ByLaws, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Resolutions, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee - Procedure 18, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 31 (Grievance Procedure), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Academic Assembly -- History, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- New Library Director Search, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Ad Hoc Committee -- Research Leaves, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Joint Meetings of Steering Committee and Standing Committee Members, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Steering Committee -- Miscellany, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- "Current", 1977 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ByLaws, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Academic Assembly -- Resolutions, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Report, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 18 (Library Personnel Office Files), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 31 (Grievance Procedure), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Economic Status of Librarians, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- General Legislation of the University Faculty & FCR & Extracts from its records, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Professional Development Committee -- Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Professional Development Committee -- Annual Reports, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Joint Meetings of Steering Committee and Standing Committee Members, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Standing Committee -- Duties, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Steering Committee, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Steering Committee -- Agenda, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Steering Committee Election, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Academic Assembly: Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- ByLaws, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Academic Assembly: resolutions, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee --Minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Hazen Affair), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Project Staff), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Travel), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 18 (Library Personnel Office Files), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- miscellaneous, 1979-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Economic Status Committee -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Professional Development, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Professional Development -- Annual Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Joint Meeting of Standing Committee and Steering Committee Members, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Standing Committee -- Duties, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Standing Committees -- annual reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Standing Committees -- Miscellany, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Steering Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, agendas, etc., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Resolutions, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Academic Assembly -- History, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Project Staff), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Travel), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 31 (Grievance Procedure, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Economic Status Committee -- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Economic Status Committee -- Annual Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Orientation, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Professional Development Committee -- Annual Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Joint Meetings of Steering Committee and Standing Committee Members, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Standing Committee Nominations, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Non-Academic Assembly -- Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Committee on Economic Status of Librarians, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Faculty Membership, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13 (Project Staff), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- [Academic Personnel Policies Committee] -- Procedure 23 (Travel), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Economic Status Committee -- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Economic Status Committee -- Annual Reports, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Standing Committee Nominations, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, agendas, etc., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Non-Academic Assembly, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Minutes, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Academic Orientation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Faculty Membership, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Reports, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee - Procedure 13 (Project Staff), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee - Procedure 34, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee - Procedure 39 (Search Procedures), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Economic Status Committee, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Professional Development Committee -- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Standing Committee -- Correspondence, roster, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, agendas, etc., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Steering Committee -- correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Steering Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Non-Academic Assembly, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Minutes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- ByLaws, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Annual Reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Economic Status Committee, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- Academic Assembly -- History, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Professional Development, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Standing Committees, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Steering Committee -- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Minutes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Resolution, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Survey Results I, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Survey Results II, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 28 (Evaluation Procedure), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Economic Status Committee, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Events and Activities, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- History, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Orientation Committee, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Professional Development, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Public Services Forum -- Archives, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Working Group on Computerized Reference Services, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Academic Assembly -- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 39 (Search Procedures), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Membership, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Orientation Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Professional Development Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Standing Committee -- Nominations, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Steering Committee -- Election, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Steering Committee -- Miscellany, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Working Group on Computerized Reference Services, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Minutes, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Academic Personnel Policies, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, Annual Report, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Events and Activities, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Professional Development Committee -- Minutes, Correspondence, etc., 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Steering Committee -- Minutes, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Working Group on Computerized Reference Services, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Minutes, Correspondence, Programs, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, Annual Report, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 44 (Leaves), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Economic Status Committee -- Annual Reports, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Orientation Committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Professional Development Committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Standing Committees, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Steering Committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Orientation Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Professional Development Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Steering Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Minutes, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Economic Status Committee -- Annual Reports, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Orientation, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Standing Committee on Resources and Services, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- ByLaws, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Minutes, Annual Reports, Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Economic Status Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- History, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Orientation, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Professional Development -- Annual Reports, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Standing Committees, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Support Staff Development Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Minutes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Economic Status Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- History, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Orientation Committee -- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Orientation Committee -- Notes, Agendas, etc., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Steering Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Minutes, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Academic Personnel Policies Committee -- Procedure 13, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Orientation Committee -- Chair's File, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Orientation Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Orientation Committee -- General Files, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Orientation Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Standing Committees, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Minutes, misc., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Council of Librarians, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Economic Status Committee, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Orientation, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Standing Committee Annual Reports, Rosters, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Steering Committee, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Agendas, Programs, Announcements, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- ByLaws, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Council of Librarians, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Orientation Committee, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
- Orientation Handouts, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Steering Committee, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)